arjun ks

Senior Program coordinator - oracle India Limited

Bangalore City, Karnataka - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/arjun-ks/8e9247624a5095b4

Seeking a position in a company where I can use my familiarity of the field and my educational background for the profit of the company. My individuality as well as past know-how should help me in causative to the overall intensification of the company.

Snaps **Expertise, Certification and Training** ✓ I am a Post Graduate in MBA with a total work experience of 6.8 years ☑ 3.3 years in IT. Currently working as a Senior Program coordinator. 3.5 years in BPO voice support, Good work ethics with excellent communication and interpersonal skills. ✓ Capable to delve into the new leading Technologies. Pro active and self starter with the great ability of leadership. Ability to work well in both a team environment and individually. Able to handle multiple projects under tight deadlines. Able to develop excellent rapport with peers, professionals and managers. ✓ Trained on PMP (project management professional) Course ✓ Diploma in Office Application {Ms-excel, Ms-word & Ms PowerPoint} ✓ Diploma in Tally 9.0 ✓ Milestone 2.0 from Infosys ✓ Coach the coach from Infosys Analytical ability from Infosys ✓ Diffusion skills from Infosys Personality development program from Bouyance ✓ National entrepreneurship network training from NEN

Willing to relocate to: Bangalore, Karnataka

WORK EXPERIENCE

senior program coordinator

oracle - Bengaluru, Karnataka -

2014 to Present

Managing Oracle's LMS system and assist all processes supporting Employee/Partner trainings, registrations, and online publication, also provide support for Oracle's LMS systems.

Process Specialist

Infosys - Bengaluru, Karnataka -

https://www.indeed.com/r/arjun-ks/8e9247624a5095b4?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

July 2011 to December 2014

Responsibility Areas:

- **=** Daily, Weekly and Monthly performance monitoring.
- **=** Quality monitoring of advisors and to identify area of improvement.
- = Customer satisfaction monitoring and providing feedback to improve customer experience.
- = Facilitating interactions with various support functions such as HR, Command centre (work force management team), finance, and transport teams.
- **=** Preparing Balance Score Card for the associates.
- **=** Matching the contract of the client and rostering agents.
- = Manage sectors on a shift basis.
- **=** Seat utilization plan. (Physical Resource allocation)
- **=** Coaching and mentoring the team members to improve on productivity and accuracy.
- = Holding Process review meetings with the senior management to review performance on an ongoing basis.
- = Imparting training to team members on regular basis.
- = Mentor new team leaders on the Floor. Has been a technical training resource for all New Hires including Team Leaders.
- **=** Have been conducting the Operations orientation programs for the new joiners on the floor.
- **=** Manage escalated customer enquiries / complaints, Share best practices across the
- = Process & facilitate process improvements initiatives.

= Monitoring and evaluating the existing processes, performance and SOPs of each agent against committed SLA's.
Imparting timely feedback and reporting to the India and UK leadership team on process.
EDUCATION
mba in human resource
sikkim manipal university - Bengaluru, Karnataka
June 2012 to June 2014
B.COM. in Marketing, Accountancy
College Bangalore University - Bengaluru, Karnataka
2011
SKILLS
PMP trained six sigma yellow belt
LINKS
https://www.linkedin.com/in/arjun-k-s-31388627/
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION
Areas of Expertise
https://www.linkedin.com/in/arjun-k-s-31388627/
 ✓ Part of Recruitment team to hire process executives for Organization. ✓ Possess excellent interpersonal, communication and organizational skills with proven abilities in team management, customer relationship management and planning. ✓ Able to coordinate with different support teams like Training, MIS, Technology and Quality to successfully implement projects

✓	Able to manage teams as per SOPs (Standard Operating Procedures) ISO [] and ensure	
con	npliance to SLA's and international standards.	
✓	Overseeing operations and ensuring achievement of desired objectives.	
✓	Driving day-to-day functions with key focus on bottom line profitability by ensuring optimal	
Resource utilization.		
✓	People Management & Team Building	
✓	Training, development, work allocation & goal setting and performance appraisal of executives.	
✓	Putting systemic quality monitoring procedures in place to ensure SLA's are met & exceeded.	
✓	Anticipate, organize & present information needed by management & client. Putting Security	
mea	asures in place to ensure information security & data integrity.	
Ach	ievements	
Multiple appreciations from Managers and Requesters for being customer centric and proactive		
✓	Throughout the carrier rating was "Significantly above the peer group"	
✓	Received number of appreciation mails from client and as well from management.	
Professional Competence		
✓	Hardworking Team Player with good communication & interpersonal skills.	
✓	Mentored new joiners, organized sessions and training for the process.	
✓	Willing to learn new concepts and take up larger responsibilities.	
✓	Have good understanding of SLA and how they relate to my performance in order to deliver	
according to client expectations.		
✓	Have working knowledge of staffing practices at the shift level to manage staffing to meet	
day to day needs.		
✓	Have broad understanding of complaint handling guidelines and procedures in use to resolve	
and/or escalate relevant issues.		
✓	Have proactively identified opportunities to exceed goals and targets, recovered from setbacks ${\sf C}$	
quickly, and identified newer ways to optimize resources needed to attain objectives.		